

KAYLEE CARSTENS

Software Engineer Student

About Me

Despite being reserved, I have excellent analytical skills, as well as solid interpersonal skills. I am capable of adapting to changes and learning new things. I work efficiently and can be relied upon to finish a project on time. My responsibilities are taken seriously, consistently going above and beyond; doing everything possible to exceed expectations.



(+27) 69 156 0988



carstenskaylee@gmail.com



161 Tamarisk Avenue Wonderboom, Pretoria

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- C#
- SQL
- Excel
- PowerPoint

Characteristics

- Reserved
- Analytical
- Interpersonal skills
- Adaptability
- Curios
- Efficient
- Reliable
- Diligent
- Committed

General Information

English Afrikaans Driver's License Reliable car

Experience

Tutor

2022 - 2023

Life Guard (Part-Time) 2017 - 2022

Swim Coach 2017 - 2022

Education

Hoërskool Overkruin Matric 2021

Belguim ITversity

Bachelor Degree of Computer Science 2022 - Current

School Participation

Swimming Life Saving 2018 - 2021

First Aid 2019

Choir 2019